<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCareApp</string>
    <string name="organization_name">The CARE Foundation</string>
    <string name="lucious_info">When Lucious first came to us at 3 months of age, we knew he had some health problems.
        He had already had eye surgery to fix an issue with one of his eyelids. We often provide permanent homes for
        exotic non-releasable animals that are hard to place with other zoos and sanctuaries due to health or behavioral issues, so Lucious was a perfect fit for us. \n \n
        However, as he started to mature, we noticed that he was less coordinated than he should be for his age. The amazing veterinarians we work with found he had
        an ear infection which we treated with antibiotics right away. Unfortunately, the problem persisted and one day we found Lucious unable to stand and very disoriented.
        We immediately drove him to one of our vets who thought perhaps he had a damaged neck vertebrae, which can sometimes happen with active young lions. \n \n
        Early the next morning, our head trainers drove Lucious to specialists at the University of Florida in Gainesville (about two hours from our sanctuary).
        He has several tests including an MRI and specialized blood panels, and was seen by the heads of several veterinary departments. The final diagnosis came
        in as Hypovitaminosis, a genetic disorder that affects a small population of lions in captivity. In short, Hypovitaminosis is a vitamin A deficiency
        which results in enlarged bones in the head and necks of lions, which can but pressure on the brain affecting motor functions such as balance and coordination.</string>
    <string name="map_description">Scalable map of The CARE Foundation</string>
    <string name="hours_label">Hours</string>
    <string name="contact_label">Contact</string>
    <string name="location_label">Location</string>
    <string name="contact_text">Contact: 407-247-8948</string>
    <string name="location_text">Location:\n4609 West Ponkan Road\nApopka, FL 32712</string>
    <string name="hours_text">Hours: Tours by Appointment Only</string>
    <string name="map_button">Facility Map</string>
    <string name="animals_button">Our Animals</string>
</resources>
